



Ting-An Lee

- UX / UI / WEB DESIGNER -

BIOGRAPHY

I'm an experienced Interaction Designer from Taiwan. I have 3 years of mobile and web design experience and highly skilled in mobile UX, web design, and prototyping.

Date of birth: 09 August 1990r.

Address: Taipei City, Taiwan

Marital status: Unmarried

Phone: +886-984-110-611

E-mail: andy790809@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR UX / UI / WEB DESIGNER | 07.2016-PERESNT XUENN PTE LTD

Discussing the customer requirements with PM, responsible for designing and planning of the company's products UX, and carried out the product UI design, as well as the web slicing (HTML, CSS, JQuery).

SENIOR UX / UI / WEB DESIGNER | 11.2015-07.2016 TEBUYGLOGLE CO., LTD

Responsible for designing the UI and UX of cross-border EC website, which about the planning, flow, prototyping, final UI designing. And led two co-walker to discuss the product process and trend.

JUNIOR WEB DESIGNER | 10.2012-10.2013 REDLIULI CO., LTD

Responsible for designing the UI, UX and slicing of company website.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE | 06.2014-07.2014

TATUNG UNIVERSITY - INTERFACE INTERACTION LAB.

- \mbox{HCI} , User Experience Design, Digital Art, Touch User Interface & Multimedia design.

BACHELOR OF ART | 06.2014-07.2014

TATUNG UNIVERSITY - DEPARTMENT OF MEDIA DESIGN

- Mass communication theory, Multi-media design and Digital art.

2

LANGUAGES





SKILLS

01. Computer

- Sketch
- Axure
- Framer.js
- · Adobe PS, AI & AE
- Sublime
- Xmind

02. Knowledge

- Web & Mobile User Experience & Interaction Design
- Web & Mobile Planning
- HTML, CSS & JS
- Prototyping
- Guildline Principle
- Google Analytics

INTERESTS







PHOTOGRAPH

DRAWING

TRAVELS